Guide to the George E. Stonebridge Photograph Collection 1897-1918 (Bulk 1899-1904) PR 66
New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Prints and manuscript material
  - Copy Prints, #s 7001-7010, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 20)
  - Copy Prints, #s 7011-7020, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 21)
  - Copy Prints, #s 7045-7141, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 22)
  - Copy prints, unnumbered, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 23)
  - Photograph Album, Croton Cornell Dam Strike, 1900 Apr. 21 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 24)
  - Stonebridge's Logbook, undated (Offsite-box 71, Folder 25)
  - Grammar School records, Certificates of Merit, Jury Duty certificates, 1872-1875, 1898, 1920's (Offsite-box 71, Folder 26)
    Separated Materials Note
    There are three additional oversize Certificates of Merit issued to Stonebridge in the Certificate File, PR 14.
  - Oversize mounted prints, undated (Offsite-box 72)